Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[bright music]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
[church bells tolling]
- Bah!
Humbug!
[clock chimes]
Oh, hush!
Confounded chimes!
Wherever I go all
I see is this clock
staring back at me.
No good in funerals.
Marley wouldn't have
approved himself.
Waste of money!
Waste of time!
Hey, hey!
Get off me!
-- Oh!
-- Get off!
- Get off me!
- All right, everyone out.
- [Man] Who are you?
- Head of the BBC.
- [Woman] That was a Twix.
- Get out!
- All right.
Plan B it is.
[man grunts]
- Coats.
- Yes!
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
- You said I'd be
taking over as Scrooge.
- No, I'm playing Scrooge,
that's why I've got the nose.
You're playing the Ghost
of Christmas Yet to Come.
- He doesn't have any lines.
- The cast said they'd
walk if you played Scrooge.
- What, the whole cast?
I'm the leading actor.
- No, you're the worst
actor in the company.
[Audience] Aww!
- Auntie Diana, you promised.
Just hurry up.
Well, you'll have to do
it over the phone, then.
- Annie, Annie!
- What, what?
- I can't remember
any of my lines.
- Again?
- It's the nerves.
- Come with me.
- What if you become ill?
- I won't!
- What if you get injured?
- I would have to be
completely incapacitated
to pull out now.
- Really?
- Get in there!
[shouting]
- Just stop, stop.
Good evening, BBC viewers.
Unfortunately, the cast
of The Christmas Carol
have all been taken ill.
[man struggling]
Just get off!
It's my microphone, mine!
But don't worry, the Cornley
Polytechnic Drama Society
happened to be passing
by and will be filling in
with special guest
narrator, Sandra's aunt,
Dame Diana Rigg.
Please enjoy A Christmas Carol.
[bright music]
[keyboard clacking]
[wind howling]
[church bell tolling]
- Bah!
Humbug!
Hush, confounded chimes!
Everywhere I go all I
see is that damned clock.
Everywhere I go.
All I see is that damned clock
staring back at me!
Ah!
No good in funerals anyhow.
Marley wouldn't approve himself.
Waste of money.
Waste of time.
[dramatic music]
- [Aunt Diana] Marley
was dead to begin with.
There was no doubt
whatever about that.
[crashing]
The register of his
burial was signed
by the solemn undertaker
and of course,
the only mourner, his
partner, Mr. Scrooge.
[coffin crashes]
[Marley crashes]
[Marley groaning]
[Marley sputtering]
[dramatic music]
[keyboard clacking]
- [Sandra] Auntie
Diana, you're on, go.
- On Christmas Eve, Scrooge
walked into his counting house.
He was a tightfisted,
hand on the grindstone,
a squeezing, wrenching,
grasping, scraping,
covetous old sinner who
was as hard as flint.
The weather was biting.
But cold and heat had
little influence on Scrooge.
No warms could warm him, no
wintry weather could chill him.
No wind that blew
was bitterer than he.
[Scrooge shouting]
- Stop it, stop it!
Could you stop?
Ow!
- [Aunt Diana] There was
not a man, woman, or child
in London who chose to walk
close to Scrooge in the street.
- Oh!
- Go, get off!
- [Aunt Diana] But as
long as he was able
to go about his
business with thrift
-and count his coins,
-[door rattling]
what did Scrooge care?
- Merry Christmas, Mr. Scrooge.
Merry Christmas,
Uncle, God save you.
- Bah, humbug!
- Christmas, a humbug?
Uncle, you don't
mean that, I'm sure.
- I do, Frances.
What's Christmas but another
time to find yourself
a year older and
not an hour richer?
- Oh.
- Every idiot who goes
about with merry Christmas
on his lips should be
boiled with his own pudding
and buried with a stick of
holly through his heart.
- Oh!
- Wipe that stupid
smile from your face.
- I have every reason
to smile, Uncle,
and make merry at
this time of year.
- What reason have
you to be merry?
You're poor enough.
- What reason have
you to be dismal?
You're rich enough.
- What else can I
be when I live in
such a world of fools as this?
- Why is one a fool
for wishing her uncle
a merry Christmas?
- Because it does you no good.
- Does me no good?
It is the one time in the
long calendar of the year
when men and women can open
their shut up hearts freely
and hold out their hands
to those below them
as their true companions.
- Fine speech, Frances,
you belong in Parliament.
- Christmas, Uncle,
though it has never
put a scrap of gold in my
pocket, has done me good
and will do me good
-[glue can clatters]
-and I say God bless it.
- Miss Frances!
[door bangs shut]
[gun clatters]
What a pleasure
it is to see you.
- Well, merry
Christmas, Bob Cratchit.
- [laughs] A merry
Christmas to you, too.
We hear a knock at the door.
[knocking]
Oh, a knock at the door!
- Oh, that must be
the lovely couple
raising money for the orphanage.
What merry bold and
charitable souls they are.
- Have I the pleasure of
addressing Mr. Scrooge
or Mr. Marley?
- Mr. Marley died seven
years ago this very day.
- Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
We're raising money
for the orphanage
to care for the sickly and
make provision for the poor,
like young Jane here.
- On the shelf, Bugsworth.
- Yes, Mr. Scrooge.
Ah, Merry Christmas,
Miss Frances.
- And to you.
- Ah, let me help
you Mr. Scrooge.
Oh, no!
He's completely incapacitated.
Don't worry, I'll step in.
- I'm fine!
- Humbug.
- Get out, Bugsworth!
- What shall I put you
down for, Mr. Scrooge?
- Nothing.
- You wish to be anonymous?
- I wish to be left
alone and keep my money.
- What would you
want for the needy?
- That they should die and
decrease the surplus population!
- I have not much
in my coin purse.
- Fear not, Mr. Cratchit,
you are poorer than most.
- But what little I
have you are welcome to.
I'm afraid there is only a
single penny I have saved.
- You would part
with your only coin?
- Yes.
- Do you not need
it for your family?
- No.
- Oh, thank you, Mr. Cratchit.
You'd give all you
have to charity.
- No.
- No?
You don't want to
give to charity?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- No.
- You have to make a choice.
Make a choice, will
you give them the coin?
- Yes.
- Thank you!
- This bag was made in China.
- God bless you, Jane.
May the generosity
of the goodly people
of London town keep you
merry this Christmas.
- Uh, merry Christmas,
Miss Frances.
- Merry Christmas, Mr. Cratchit.
- And to you.
- Don't be cross,
Uncle, say you'll come
and dine with us tomorrow.
- No, Frances, I shall
spend Christmas alone.
Kindly keep Christmas
in your own way
and let me keep it in mine.
- Keep it?
But you don't keep it!
- Let me leave it alone, then.
- Very well, Uncle, if
you change your mind
you have our address.
[chair clatters]
Merry Christmas.
[quietly] Sorry.
Can we just, look...
[quietly] Okay, Jane.
And my coat, and my coat.
Just, don't look,
Bob, don't look.
Okay, all right.
Let's get on me coat.
Okay.
Open it.
Open the door, open the door.
Jane, open the door.
And a merry Christmas
to you, Bob Cratchit.
[door bangs shut]
- You'll want all day
tomorrow, I suppose.
- If it's quite convenient, sir.
- It's not convenient,
Bob Cratchit.
- Christmas comes
but once a year.
Look outside at the people
going about their
business with glee.
This is not a time for
money but for family
and mine would
appreciate me home, sir.
- Spare me your foolish
humbug, Cratchit.
- I...
I uh...
I, I...
I, I, uh, I...
I am not a rich man.
[books clattering]
If I can spend Christmas
with my family,
I would be content to
gnaw...
upon a bone or sleep
on a bed of warts.
[door bangs shut]
- Fine, Cratchit,
take the whole day.
- Uoy sselb.
- Bless you.
- Thank you.
- Humbug!
But be here all the
earlier the next morning!
- [Cratchit] Wang!
[dramatic music]
[owl hoots]
[keys jangling]
[Scrooge gasps]
- Jacob Marley?
- Scroo--
[knocker clanks]
[muffled] Scrooge!
- Humbug.
- [Aunt Diana] Scrooge,
shaken by the vision,
went to search the
rooms of his house
for signs of an intruder.
Finding nothing untoward,
he returned to his bedroom,
secure in the knowledge the
house was completely empty,
other than Scrooge.
[bell rings]
[clapper splats]
[bells ringing]
[door bangs shut]
[locks clicking]
- [Man] [whispers] I'll get it.
- [Ghostly Voice] Scrooge!
- Who's there?
- [Ghostly Voice]
Ebenezer Scrooge!
- Humbug!
[lightning crashes]
What trickery is this?
Who are you?
- In life, I was your
partner, Jacob Marley.
You don't believe in me?
[thunder crashing]
- I do not.
- Why do you doubt your senses?
- Because a little
thing effects them.
You may be an
undigested bit of beef!
A blot of mustard.
There's more of gravy
than the grave about you.
[Marley shouts]
[chains rattling]
[Marley crashing]
Proceed, dreadful apparition!
Why do you trouble me?
- If a spirit goes
not forth in life,
it is condemned to
do so after death.
I am doomed to wander
through the world
and witness what I cannot share.
I wear the chain
I forged in life.
I made it link by
link and yard by yard.
[crashing]
[chain clanking]
You must listen!
My time is nearly gone.
[Marley thudding]
Oh, how I wish I could cast
off these cursed chains!
I am made captive by my deeds.
But like me, Scrooge,
you have girded yourself
a great chain, which in time
shall hang heavy around you.
[locks clicking]
[door rattling]
- Stay away, vile spirit!
I wish to see no more of you.
- [Marley] Unlock the door.
- Begone!
[door rattling]
- Undo the bottom one.
You will be haunted
by three spirits.
Without their visits,
you cannot hope
to shun the path I tread.
Expect the first when
the bell tolls one.
Farewell, Scrooge.
Scrooge.
[chains jangling]
- [Aunt Diana] Scrooge
was left alone again.
He looked out
through his window,
which was locked
shut, undisturbed,
just as it was before
the ghost arrived.
Resolved to forget
what he'd experienced,
Scrooge went to bed
and blew out the light.
[bright music]
[clock chimes]
[eerie music]
- Are you the spirit whose
coming was foretold to me?
- I am.
- Who and what are you?
- Come close and
I shall tell you.
I am the Ghost of
Christmas Past.
I shine with the light of a
thousand Christmases gone.
- [Scrooge] I have never
seen your like before.
May I look closer?
- [Man] No, no, no, no, no!
It's, oh, oh!
- By my light you shall
see the truth of your past.
Take me in your hand, Scrooge.
[Scrooge grunts]
Your past is hidden
beyond these walls.
Step through with me.
- I am mortal, spirit, I cannot.
- By my light you shall.
[dresser creaking]
-[dresser crashes]
-- Humbug, ah!
- This way, Mr. Scrooge.
Oh!
- [Aunt Diana] And with that,
Scrooge and the spirit
disappeared from his bedroom.
- [Ghost Of Christmas Past]
[quietly] Take me through,
I don't have arms.
- [Scrooge] [quietly]
Alright, just go.
- [Ghost Of Christmas
Past] Tip me.
Tip me, tip me!
[Scrooge groans]
- You're not moving, just...
- [Ghost Of
Christmas Past] Wait.
Have we disappeared?
- [Scrooge] Yes, shh.
- [Aunt Diana]
Scrooge found himself
soaring over open
fields and woodland.
- Oh, unnatural spirit,
will we not fall?
- We shall not, Mr. Scrooge.
[birds cawing]
- Where are you taking me?
- My light shall show you
the man you once were.
[electronic chiming]
[man mumbling]
- [Computer] Welcome
to Greenscreen 1-2-3,
where with just one click,
you can be on a beach
or at the Eiffel Tower.
Overlay your own
exciting footage.
- Yeah, I think Robert would
make a great leading actor.
- Oh, come on.
It's Ebenezer Scrooge,
not Ebenezer Huge.
[merry music]
- [Scrooge] Ow!
Ow!
Ah!
Robert!
Stop!
Stop it, ow!
Stop it!
This is becoming--
Don't!
Get off!
Bloody get off!
- [Man] Oh!
Oh, no!
[Robert growls]
[chair smashes]
- Oh, no, he's
completely incapacitated.
- No, I'm not!
- Humbug!
- I'm fine!
[electronic chiming]
- I want to be in a
grownup relationship.
I don't want to be
dating Max anymore.
- When are you gonna do it?
- After we finish
Christmas Carol.
- Yeah.
[electronic chiming]
[Scrooge sighs]
- Good heavens, I
know this place.
I grew up here.
This is where Belle
and I would court.
And there we are.
- I'm sorry, Ebenezer.
We cannot be
together any longer.
- Why, my love?
- Another idol has displaced
me that you love more.
- [stammering] Who is
this idol you speak of?
There is no one else.
- The pursuit of wealth
and gain engrosses you.
- I don't understand.
- You have grown
hard and unfeeling.
Like your partner, Mr. Marley.
- Please, don't leave me.
- Our contract is an old one,
made when we were both poor.
- I can change.
- You are changed.
When it was made, you
were a different man.
I release you with
a heart full of love
for the man you once were.
Goodbye, my dearest.
Good--
- Oh, spirit, why do you
delight in torturing me?
- Dry your tears, Ebenezer,
you must to bed before
the other spirits arrive.
[bells tolling]
[bright music]
[pizza splats]
- [Man] Oh, no.
Sorry, mate, sorry.
- [Aunt Diana] And just
as Jacob Marley said,
upon the stroke of two,
[clock chimes twice]
Scrooge heard the merry
sound of laughter.
- [crying] Ho, ho, ho.
Hello, Scrooge.
- Who are you, spirit?
- I am the Ghost of
Christmas Present.
I am cheer, I am joy, [voice
breaking] I am Christmas.
Come and know me better, man.
- Oh, spirit, I have seen
enough for one night.
I cannot bear
another heartbreak.
I beg you, leave me be.
Haunt me no longer.
[crashing]
- Humbug.
[Scrooge groaning]
Haunt me no longer.
No, me!
- Get off!
Help me out.
- Me, me!
[crashing]
- Worry not, Scrooge.
Your journey with me shall
not be one of heartbreak,
but of mirth.
Now, come, you look hungry.
- What is all this?
- Why, 'tis the
bounty of Christmas.
Ho, ho, ho!
-- I don't believe
-[crashing]
you have merely come to feed me.
Tell me, spirit, the
purpose of your visit.
- Each year you have
shunned the present,
but this year you will
mark the lessons it holds.
[bottle shattering]
[Robert groaning]
- Very well.
Conduct me where you will.
If you have aught to
teach me, I shall listen
and profit by it.
- Then follow me to
the street, Scrooge.
- Show me something
I may smile upon.
[gasps] Jacobi!
- Ho, ho, ho!
[arrow darting]
[Jacobi choking]
- All gone now, he's
completely incapaci-
oh, for God's sake.
Right, come on, Jacobi.
- Uh, come down to
the street, Scrooge,
and see how the goodly
people celebrate Christmas.
A day where all mankind
can forget their position
and go about with
glee and good tidings.
Masters and servants,
judges and scoundrels,
landlords and lodgers, can
all make merry together
and wish each other well.
Do you recognize
this house, Scrooge?
- Aye, it is Bob
Cratchit's house for sure.
Here comes his youngest,
Tiny Tim, walking home.
- Ah, Tiny Tim, the sweetest,
dearest boy that there ever was.
[crashing]
- Ho, ho, ho!
Come, Scrooge, look
through the window
and observe how these
humble folk live.
- I've had the children
clean up before we eat.
What'll we be having for
Christmas dinner, Bob?
Bob?
- A goose.
- Oh, Bob, you saved up
for it, how wonderful.
- Anything for you, my sweet.
A drop to drink?
- Oh, why thank you.
How was Tiny Tim at church?
- As good as gold and better.
He told me coming home
he hoped people saw him
because he was a cripple
and it might be pleasant
for them to remember
on Christmas day
who made lame beggars
walk and blind men see.
Enough wine for you, my dear?
- Plenty.
I pray for him every day.
Here he comes now.
- Hello, Mama.
- Tim, come here, my little boy.
- Lift me in your arms, Papa.
Whee.
- Oh, Tim, you do
look frail of late.
- I am frail.
Frail and ill.
Achoo.
- Uoy sselb.
- Sit up to the
table, my little Tim.
- Oh, Mama.
- Now let us raise a
glass to Mr. Scrooge,
the founder of the...
feast.
- The founder of
the feast, indeed.
That hard, unfeeling
scoundrel is the cause
of our suffering.
- Mr. Scrooge has not
the kind family I have.
I pity him.
- Mm.
- Alone on Christmas day.
We may be poor, but we
are rich in company.
Eat, Father.
- Oof!
- There is a wealth Mr.
Scrooge may never know.
[cup thunks]
To Mr. Scrooge.
- [Both] [weakly] The
founder of the feast.
-- God bless us--
-[door bangs shut]
- God bless us, everyone.
- A remarkable boy.
Tell me, spirit, if
Tiny Tim will live.
- I see a vacant seat and
a crutch without an owner.
- Do I really pay Bob so poorly?
They have such a meager feast.
What a fine family they are.
Tiny Tim is such a brave boy.
Mrs. Cratchit such a
loyal and devoted woman.
- But they should
get on with dying
and decrease the surplus
population, should they not?
What more can you afford to pay?
- I don't only care
about myself, do I?
- Come, there is more to see.
Do you recognize
this house, Scrooge?
- It belongs to
my niece, Frances.
There she is now.
Oh, uh...
[door bangs shut]
Oh, dear.
It looks like they've
got the decorators in.
I'm sure they'll be
done any moment now.
And there we are, they're done.
[all laughing]
- Is it a vegetable?
- Not a vegetable, no.
- Mineral, then?
- Not a mineral,
which leaves you with?
- Animal.
- Quite so.
- Alive?
- More or less.
- Oh, my dear Frances,
why must you always
be so cryptic?
[Frances laughs]
Is this animal
disagreeable or friendly?
- Oh, disagreeable for sure.
- Does it growl?
- Sometimes.
- Is it found in England?
- It's found in London, Topper.
- A horse.
- No, but it says nay
more than a horse does.
[all laughing]
[laughs]
- Is it a pig?
- Is it a fox?
- Is this animal domesticated?
- Hardly.
- Frances, I know what it is.
[clears throat]
A disagreeable creature,
but none of these?
It is your uncle,
Ebenezer Scrooge.
- It is, it is!
Oh, bravo, Topper.
Oh.
- A disagreeable creature,
is that what they think?
- And a growling one.
But what does Scrooge care
what these fools believe?
- I don't care.
- Indeed.
More or less dead,
hardly domesticated.
What childish blabber.
- I care perhaps a little.
- The time has
come for me to away
and let in another spirit
before Christmas day.
I'm all right, it's all right.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, it's all
right, you're fine.
- Sorry, sorry.
[bell tolls thrice]
[crashing]
Sorry, mate, sorry!
[Scrooge shudders]
[eerie music]
[thumping]
[Scrooge gasps]
- Come on!
Come on!
[Ghost thudding]
[Ghost moans]
- Are you the Ghost of
Christmas Yet to Come?
[electronic chiming]
- [Max] Sandra.
- I've got good news.
That agent just called.
He's going to take
me on. [laughs]
He said the exposure
from Christmas Carol
will easily get me that advert.
I'll never have to work with
this bunch of freaks again.
[electronic chiming]
- [Audience] Aww!
[dramatic music]
- I don't suppose anyone will
attend the old goat's funeral.
[coffin creaks]
- He never gave a
penny to charity.
He stole from the poor.
- Selfish.
- Spirit.
Show me some tenderness
connected with the death
or this dark conversation
will be forever present to me.
[Ghost grunts]
[mask thumps window]
- [sobs] Oh, my poor Tim.
Be at peace, my dear, sweet boy.
-[coffin crashes open]
-[Jacobi shouting]
[Jacobi wheezing]
- Why would you have
put him in the coffin?
- [Robert] Well, how
else am I supposed
to keep him contained?
[bell tolling]
[Ghost thumps gate]
Oh.
- Oh, come on!
[Robert grunts]
[thumps gate]
- Yes, he died a
week ago, I heard.
- Good lord, I thought
he'd never die.
[both laughing]
- Well, I certainly
shan't miss him.
- Nor I.
He was very unpopular.
[arm thumps statue]
- Spirit.
Are these the shadows
of things that will be
or are they the shadow of
things that may only be?
[thunder crashing]
Oh!
Spirit!
A man may change the
course of his life.
Spirit, I...
Spirit, I am sorry.
I have been greedy and selfish.
I have served
myself before others
and shut out the gift
of their kindnesses.
I am sorry to everyone.
All of you.
I've taken you all for granted.
I thought I wanted to
go it alone, but...
Truth is I'd be
lost without you.
In fact, I believe
I am not feeling at all well.
I think I may be
completely incapacitated.
Scrooge.
- What?
- I'm completely
incapacitated, Mr. Scrooge.
- Chris, I don't
know what to say.
I couldn't.
- You have to.
We are all counting
on our lead actor.
- Chris, it's your part
and you should finish it.
I'm not gonna take your role.
- Well, why don't
we do it together?
- No, I'll do it.
Humbug!
[all laughing]
Quickly, we have to
finish the thing.
[all chattering]
Here we are, come on, quickly.
Hurry up!
That's it, this way.
Up to the bedroom,
come on, quickly.
Hurry up, there's still time.
We can still make it
work, come on, quickly!
- Scrooge fell before the spirit
and woke to find himself in bed.
- Good morning!
I shall live in the past,
present, and the future.
The spirits of all three
shall strive within me.
You there, child,
what day is it?
- It's Christmas day!
- Christmas day, oh,
Jacob Marley be praised!
Wait there, for I must
speak with you a moment.
I shall have that girl
run to the poulterers
and fetch the plumpest bird
she can find in the shop.
Merry Christmas everyone!
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you, sir!
-Merry Christmas.
-- Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas to
one and all! [laughs]
Merry--
- Excuse me, are
you playing Scrooge?
- No.
Chris is playing Scrooge.
- I am not playing Scrooge.
You took over as Scrooge.
- I only took over
as Scrooge because
you forced me to
take over as Scrooge.
- I did not force you
to take over as Scrooge.
If anything, you forced
me to play Scrooge
by being such a bad actor.
- Nobody forced either
of you to play Scrooge!
You came here and
took Scrooge from me.
By force!
- Stop fighting, look,
it doesn't matter
who's playing Scrooge.
That's what we've
learnt tonight.
- It's not what I've
learned tonight.
I've learned that it
absolutely matters!
I am Scrooge!
Get them out.
- No, no, no, no.
- Come on, it's over.
- No, get, get off!
- They're using force!
They're using force!
- No no!
Chris, understudy!
- I'm Scrooge!
[all clamoring]
- Quick, the cameras!
[clamoring]
- Get off him!
Get off him, Jacobi!
[thunks]
- Which way?
- [Audience] Aww!
- We'll finish this outside!
Everyone outside!
[static buzzing]
Okay, go, go!
All right, quickly,
they're behind us.
[Robert panting]
- All right, all
right, all right,
we're still filming, so action.
- Uh, here's a better idea.
Why don't we all go
to the poulterer's
and fetch a goose?
We shall take it to
Bob Cratchit's house.
♪ Ding dong merrily on high ♪
♪ Heavenly bells are ringing ♪
♪ Ding dong merrily the sky ♪
[mumbling]
♪ La la la la ♪
♪ Gloria ♪
♪ Hosannah in excelsis ♪
- Now, everyone, we must search
for the plumpest
goose we can find.
♪ Jingle bells jingle bells ♪
♪ Jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one horse open sleigh ♪
- Ah, no goose then.
But very well, Bob Cratchit,
if this is what you desire most
then it is what you shall have.
♪ For everyone at
Christmas loves goujons ♪
♪ Hey jingle bells
jingle bells ♪
♪ Jingle all the way ♪
Sorry, would you mind
if we went ahead of you?
- Yes, I would mind.
♪ Dashing through the snow ♪
- Greetings, good fellow.
- Hiya.
- I would like to purchase
these fine goujons, please.
- It's 3.99, please.
- Does anyone have any...
Do you have any money?
- No.
- I appear to have
left my coin purse
in my other britches.
- If you don't have any
money, you'll have to leave.
- Might you be able
to open your heart
to those in need at Christmas?
- I'm sorry, mate.
- Please, it's
for the Cratchits.
- Who?
- Please, we need them.
- Aye, just take
whatever you want.
Take the money, it's fine.
- Really?
We just want the goujons.
- Yeah, take them,
just don't hurt anyone.
- Yeah, yeah, bag it up, yeah.
- Merry Christmas.
♪ Jingle bells jingle
bells jingle all the way ♪
- Give us a Snickers.
Take one yourself.
- What?
- Take one yourself!
- Okay, okay!
- And this lady's
shopping's free.
- Yeah, whatever you say.
- Okay.
Merry Christmas.
- Now, everyone, we shall
return to Bob Cratchit's house
and present him with the
finest Christmas feast
he has had in all his life.
[humming]
♪ Fa la la la la la la la la ♪
Festive greetings!
We are traveling the
town to wish everyone
a merry Christmas.
- Oh.
-- Merry Christmas.
-- Happy Christmas.
- Oh, that's nice.
- Might we enter
and spread our joy
to the fine townsfolk within?
- Not without a pass.
- Oh, dear.
That is a shame.
We had hoped we might be able to
get back in the studio, but--
[alarm blaring]
- Oh, that's the fire alarm.
Um, if you could all
just make your way
out of the building and
across the courtyard.
Thank you, all of you.
- Will do.
♪ Now our gay apparel fa la ♪
Shh, shh, shh, shh!
- Oh, ho, ho!
No!
[doors bang shut]
-No!
-[pounding]
[knocks]
- Bob Cratchit.
Bob Cratchit are you in there?
- No, I'm here.
- Go round for God's sake.
Merry Christmas, Bob.
A merrier Christmas
than I have given you
in many a year.
May I come in?
[door bangs shut]
- Yes.
- Thank you, Bob.
I have come here to tell you
that I intend to
double your salary
and shall endeavor to...
- Assist your struggling family.
- To assist your
struggling family.
- [Both] Tiny Tim
shall walk again
and I shall keep
Christmas in my heart.
First, though, let us all
have a Christmas dinner.
What do you say, Bob?
- Yes.
- Merry Christmas.
[bright music]
- Okay, attention, everyone.
Sorry, um, sorry,
before we finish,
there's something I'd
like to say to Max.
- You aren't gonna
break up with me on air.
What's wrong with you?
- Break up with you?
- Yeah, I saw the video.
You said you didn't want
to be dating anymore.
- I don't want to
be dating anymore.
I want to be married.
- [Audience] Aww!
- To me?
- Yes, I...
I had a whole plan.
I was gonna propose.
- But I saw you kissing Chris.
- What?
- Yeah, I thought we
were friends and--
- What are you talking--
- Guys, look, I found something.
Look at this.
- Oh! [laughs]
Same dress.
You all right, Chris?
- Yeah.
- That's my sister.
- You were going to propose?
- Yeah.
- Right, that's it!
[door bangs shut]
I've had it.
You've ruined Christmas
again, all of you!
It wasn't enough to ruin
the production last year,
now you've sabotaged mine.
So go on, get out of here.
We are going to perform our
version from the top now!
- But it's a proposal.
- I don't care.
I'm going to give
my performance.
The only chance you
have of continuing
is if I am completely
incapacitated.
[tires screeching]
[thudding]
Oh!
- Oh, come on, Derek,
this is not about you.
- Yeah, but I... [stammering]
Oh, forget it.
- Ta-da! [laughs]
- Thank you, Auntie Diana.
[dramatic music]
[all clapping]
- And so as Tiny Tim observed--
- Please.
God bless us, ev--
[door bangs open]
- God bless us, everyone.
[bright music]